Then your position will go down -15%instead!
so it is a lever, thus it becomes a greater effect upward or downward
So I want to give you a big warning finger for that
Another mistake that Andreas Hansson has tips on
and it is not to be patient to keep the good companies you actually managed to buy
This is something that I recognize myself in very much
When you bought a share and it goes well, dare to keep it then
Don't be such that if it goes down a bit, want to take home the profit
Think of long term.
How long do you want to own this share?
How long do you want to invest this money?
This is a lesson that many beginners learn that they take home the profits too soon.
Not to be patient to go by train.